Now let's turn a thought to a task.
So press Right Option key,
say the request shown below and press the right
option key again to submit.
What this will do is this will create a new Claude
or a Codex session based on whatever you selected,
and it will send you a request as the input for that session.
And you can just look at the notch at the top
and your request would be in, sending state initially.
Once the request is sent,
you can open the chat box basically by tapping the
notch and it will have your message as well as the model's response
there itself.
So this is a really easy way for you to trigger
new tasks from anywhere across your Mac.
You don't have to switch windows, you don't have to
switch apps.
And look for, you know,
the terminal or where the Codex or Claude app is.
You just have to.
Well, if you had a thought,
you just have to unmute yourself by pressing the Right Option key and
say, what do you want to say?
Capture whatever you want to capture.
If it's a Slack link, if it's a Twitter link,
if it's a YouTube video, if it's a blog that you're reading,
you can just copy that along with your dictation
while you're dictating and you can just press the Right Option again.
You can just press submit again and it will create
a new task there and there itself.